Inventaris van het archief van het Rijksinstituut voor Oorlogsdocumentatie (RIOD), 1933-1966
Nationaal Archief, Den Haag
- NAOORLOGS ARCHIEF 1945 t/m 1966, B
  - PROCESSEN NEURENBERG, AMERICAN MILITARY TRIBUNAL, 47.
    - A.M.T. court 4, case 11 against Ernst von Weizsäcker e.a., 47.9.
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 23-03-1948 t/m 06-05-1948; 1284
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg. (Die van 11 mei ook in Duits), 07-05-1948 t/m 11-05-1948; 1285
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 12-05-1948 t/m 14-05-1948; 1286
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 15-05-1948 t/m 26-05-1948; 1287
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 27-05-1948 t/m 4 juni 1948; 1288
      - Official transoripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizaäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 07-06-1948 t/m 10-06-1948; 1289
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 11-06-1948 t/m 17-06-1948; 1290
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 18-06-1948 t/m 21-06-1948; 1291
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 22,23 juni 1948; 1292
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 24-06-1948 t/m 01-07-1948; 1293
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 02-07-1948 t/m 09-07-1948; 1294
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 12-07-1948 t/m 15-07-1948; 1295
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 16-07-1948 t/m 22-07-1948; 1296
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 23 juli 1948; 1297
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 26-07-1948 t/m 30-07-1948; 1298
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 31-07-1948 t/m 03-08-1948; 1299
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 04-08-1948 t/m 06-08-1948; 1300
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 09-08-1948 t/m 12-08-1948; 1301
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 13-08-1948 t/m 17-08-1948; 1302
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 18-08-1948 t/m 20-08-1948; 1303
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 21-08-1948 t/m 25-08-1948; 1304
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 26-08-1948 t/m 30-08-1948; 1305
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 31-08-1948 t/m 03-09-1948; 1306
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 03-09-1948 t/m 09-09-1948; 1307
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 09-09-1948 t/m 15-09-1948; 1308
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 15-09-1948 t/m 22-09-1948; 1309
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 22-09-1948 t/m 27-09-1948; 1310
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 28-09-1948 t/m 30-09-1948; 1311
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 30-09-1948 t/m 06-10-1948; 1312
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 06-10-1948 t/m 12-10-1948; 1313
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 13-10-1948 t/m 20-10-1948; 1314
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 21-10-1948 t/m 10-11-1948; 1315
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 11-11-1948 t/m 18-11-1948; 1316
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 4 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Ernst von Weizsäcker, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., apr. t/m nov. 1948, 11-04-1949 t/m 14-04-1949; 1317
        Diverse Corrections
    - A.M.T. court 5, case 7 against Wilhelm List e.a., 47.10.
      - Indictment Openingsrede tegen W. List e.a. 15 juli 1947, Vonnis 19 febr.1948; [1947, 1948]; 1318
    - A.M.T. court 5, case 12 against Wilhem von Leeb e.a., 47.11.
      - Official transcripts of AMT 5 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Wilhelm von Leeb, et al, defendants, Nürnberg., 30-12-1947 t/m 20-02-1948; 1319
      - Official transcripts of AMT 5 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Wilhelm von Leeb, et al, defendants, Nürnberg., 24-02-1948 t/m 09-04-1948; 1320
      - Official transcripts of AMT 5 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Wilhelm von Leeb, et al, defendants, Nürnberg., 12-04-1948 t/m 23-04-1948; 1321
      - Official transcripts of AMT 5 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Wilhelm von Leeb, et al, defendants, Nürnberg., 26-04-1948 t/m 06-05-1948; 1322
      - Official transcripts of AMT 5 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Wilhelm von Leeb, et al, defendants, Nürnberg., 07-04-1948 t/m 20-05-1948; 1323
      - Official transcripts of AMT 5 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Wilhelm von Leeb, et al, defendants, Nürnberg., 21-05-1948 t/m 07-06-1948; 1324
      - Official transcripts of AMT 5 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Wilhelm von Leeb, et al, defendants, Nürnberg., 08-06-1948 t/m 21-06-1948; 1325
      - Official transcripts of AMT 5 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Wilhelm von Leeb, et al, defendants, Nürnberg., 22-06-1948 t/m 06-07-1948; 1326
      - Official transcripts of AMT 5 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Wilhelm von Leeb, et al, defendants, Nürnberg., 07-07-1948 t/m 21-07-1948; 1327
      - Official transcripts of AMT 5 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Wilhelm von Leeb, et al, defendants, Nürnberg., 22-07-1948 t/m 04-08-1948; 1328
      - Official transcripts of AMT 5 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Wilhelm von Leeb, et al, defendants, Nürnberg., 05-08-1948 t/m 27-10-1948; 1329
      - Official transcripts of AMT 5 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Wilhelm von Leeb, et al, defendants, Nürnberg., 28 okt. 1948; 1330
    - A.M.T. court 6, case 6 against Karl Krauch e.a., 47.12.
      - Basic Information: I.G. Farbenindustrie vol. I en II, 20 aug. 1947; 1331
      - Indictment (gedrukt). 3 mei 1947, Table of witnesses appearing before tribunal 6 during prosecution case-in-chief. 10 dec. 1947; Nachträge zum Dokumentenbücher I und V. Antwort auf den Antrag der Verteidigung auf einen Freispruch unter Punkt I und V und vor der Anklage in Punkt II im Bezug auf Osterreich und die Tschechoslovakei. Plaidoy über "Gründsatzliche Rechtsfragen" von Prof. Dr. Eduard Wohl. 8 jan. 1948; [1947, 1948]; 1332
      - Opening-statement against Karl Krauch e.a. 27 aug. 1947 Prelinary memorandum brief of the prosecution. 15 dec. 1947 Closing statement for the U.S.A. 10 juni 1948, [1947, 1948]; 1333
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 6 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Karl Krauch, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 14-08-1947 t/m 10-09-1947; 1334
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 6 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Karl Krauch, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 11-09-1947 t/m 01-10-1947; 1335
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 6 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Karl Krauch, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 02-10-1947 t/m 17-10-1947; 1336
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 6 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Karl Krauch, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 21-10-1947 t/m 04-11-1947; 1337
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 6 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Karl Krauch, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 05-11-1947 t/m 21-11-1947; 1338
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 6 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Karl Krauch, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 24-11-1947 t/m 02-12-1947; 1339
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 6 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Karl Krauch, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 13-12-1947 t/m 12-01-1948; 1340
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 6 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Karl Krauch, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 13-01-1948 t/m 28-01-1948; 1341
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 6 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Karl Krauch, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 29-01-1948 t/m 11-02-1948; 1342
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 6 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Karl Krauch, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 12-02-1948 t/m 25-02-1948; 1343
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 6 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Karl Krauch, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 26-02-1948 t/m 06-03-1948; 1344
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 6 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Karl Krauch, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 08-03-1948 t/m 17-03-1948; 1345
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 6 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Karl Krauch, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 18-03-1946 t/m 31-03-1948; 1346
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 6 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Karl Krauch, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 1, 2 apr. 1948; 1347
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 6 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Karl Krauch, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 03-04-1948 t/m 12-04-1948; 1348
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 6 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Karl Krauch, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 13-04-1948 t/m 20-04-1948; 1349
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 6 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Karl Krauch, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 21-04-1948 t/m 23-04-1948; 1350
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 6 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Karl Krauch, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 26-04-1948 t/m 29-04-1948; 1351
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 6 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Karl Krauch, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 30-04-1948 t/m 06-05-1948; 1352
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 6 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Karl Krauch, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 07-05-1948 t/m 02-06-1948; 1353
      - Official transcripts of the AMT 6 in the matter of the U.S.A. against Karl Krauch, et al, defendants, sitting at Nürnberg., 03-06-1948 t/m 11-06-1948; 1354
      - Judgement of the tribunal. 29, 30 juli 1948, Vonnis (Duitse tekst)30 juli 1948; 1355
      - Corrections. Joint-motions., 1356
      - Joint-motions., juni 1948; 1357
  - TRIBUNAL SUPERIEURE DE GOUVERNEMENT MILITAIRE DE LA ZONE FRANCAISE D'OCCUPATION EN ALLEMAGNE TE RASTAT., 48.
    - Beweissührung der Statsanwaltschaft gegen die Leiter der Röchlingschen Firma, deel III., jan. 1948; 1358
    - Jugement rendu in de zaak tegen Hermann Röchling e.a., 25 jan 1948; 1359
    - Indictment against the directors of the firm of Röchling. 1 juli 1948, Rapport: The Röchling-trial. feb/juli 1948; Teletype reports of Mr. Marcu on Röchling proceedings at Rastat. 13 maart 1948; 1360
  - INTERNATIONAL MILITARY TRIBUNAL FOR THE FAR EAST, TOKYO against ARAKI E.A., 49.
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 29-04-1946 t/m 12-06-1946; 1361
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 13-06-1946 t/m 21-06-1946; 1362
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 24-06-1946 t/m 03-07-1946; 1363
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 05-07-1946 t/m 24-07-1946; 1364
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 25-07-1946 t/m 02-08-1946; 1365
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 05-08-1946 t/m 13-08-1946; 1366
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 15-08-1946 t/m 28-08-1946; 1367
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 29-08-1946 t/m 06-09-1946; 1368
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 09-09-1946 t/m 17-09-1946; 1369
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 18-09-1946 t/m 25-09-1946; 1370
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 26-09-1946 t/m 04-10-1946; 1371
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 07-10-1946 t/m 15-10-1946; 1372
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 16-10-1946 t/m 23-10-1946; 1373
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 24-10-1946 t/m 01-11-1946; 1374
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 04-11-1946 t/m 08-11-1946; 1375
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 12-11-1946 t/m 18-11-1946; 1376
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 19-11-1946 t/m 27-11-1946; 1377
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 29-11-1946 t/m 07-12-1946; 1378
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 09-12-1946 t/m 16-12-1946; 1379
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 17-12-1946 t/m 24-12-1946; 1380
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 26-12-1946 t/m 03-01-1947; 1381
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 06-01-1947 t/m 13-01-1947; 1382
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 14-01-1947 t/m 22-01-1947; 1383
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 23-01-1947 t/m 29-01-1947; 1384
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 30-01-1947 t/m 27-02-1947; 1385
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 28-02-1947 t/m 11-03-1947; 1386
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 12-03-1947 t/m 20-03-1947; 1387
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 21-03-1947 t/m 08-04-1947; 1388
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 009-04-1947 t/m 18-04-1947; 1389
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 21-04-1947 t/m 29-04-1947; 1390
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 30-04-1947 t/m 12-05-1947; 1391
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 13-05-1947 t/m 21-05-1947; 1392
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 22-05-1947 t/m 03-06-1947; 1393
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 04-06-1947 t/m 13-06-1947; 1394
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 16-06-1947 t/m 06-08-1947; 1395
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 07-08-1947 t/m 15-08-1947; 1396
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 18-08-1947 t/m 25-08-1947; 1397
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 26-08-1947 t/m 03-09-1947; 1398
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 04-09-1947 t/m 12-09-1947; 1399
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 15-09-1947 t/m 23-09-1947; 1400
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 24-09-1947 t/m 02-10-1947; 1401
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 03-10-1947 t/m 13-10-1947; 1402
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 14-10-1947 t/m 21-10-1947; 1403
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 22-10-1947 t/m 31-10-1947; 1404
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 03-11-1947 t/m 12-11-1947; 1405
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 13-11-1947 t/m 21-11-1947; 1406
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 24-11-1947 t/m 03-12-1947; 1407
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 04-12-1947 t/m 12-12-1947; 1408
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 15-12-1947 t/m 23-12-1947; 1409
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 24-12-1947 t/m 05-01-1948; 1410
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 06-01-1948 t/m 14-01-1948; 1411
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 13-01-1948 t/m 22-01-1948; 1412
    - Official transcripts of the IMT, Tokyo against Araki, et al, defendants. (I.P.S. Netherlands Division), 23-01-1948 t/m 10-02-1948; 1413
    - Narrative Summary of record Vol. 1 t/m 4., 1414
    - Narrative Summary of record Vol. 5 t/m 11., 1415
    - Narrative Summary of record Vol. 12 t/m 21, 1416
    - Narrative Summary of record Vol 22 t/m 30, 1417
    - Narrative Summary of record Vol. 31 t/m 41, 1418
    - Narrative Summary of record Vol. 42 t/m 51, 1419
    - Summation of the prosecution. General summation I.P.S.; afzonderlijke beklaagden A t/m K; Pow Summation-appendix A, BI en BII., 1420
    - Summary of Evidence: Summations i/z de afzonderlijke beklaagden AA t/m QQ., 1421
    - Summary of Evidence: Summations i/z de afzonderlijke beklaagden RR t/m YY. Reply of prosecution to defense summation, vol. I t/m III., 1422
    - Records of Proceedings (afschriften van bandopnamen) vol. 149 t/m 150., 11-02-1948 t/m 16-02-1948; 1423
    - Records of Proceedings (afschriften van bandopnamen) vol. 151 t/m 152., 17-02-1948 t/m 19-02-1948; 1424
    - Records of Proceedings (afschriften van bandopnamen) vol, 155 t/m 157, 19-02-1948 t/m 24-02-1948; 1425
    - Records of Proceedings (afschriften van bandopnamen) vol. 158 t/m 160., 26-02-1948 t/m 02-03-1948; 1426
    - Records of Proceedings (afschriften van bandopnamen) vol. 161 t/m 164, 03-03-1948 t/m 08-03-1948; 1427
    - Records of Proceedings (afschriften van bandopnamen) vol. 165 t/m 167., 09-03-1948 t/m 12-03-1948; 1428
    - Records of Proceedings (afschriften van bandopnamen) vol. 168 t/m 171., 15-03-1948 t/m 18-03-1948; 1429
    - Records of Proceedings (afschriften van bandopnamen) vol. 172 t/m 175., 19-03-1948 t/m 24-03-1948; 1430
    - Records of Proceedings (afschriften van bandopnamen) vol. 176 t/m 179., 25-03-1948 t/m 30-03-1948; 1431
    - Records of Proceedings (afschriften van bandopnamen) vol. 180 t/m 183., 31-03-1948 t/m 05-04-1948; 1432
    - Records of Proceedings (afschriften van bandopnamen) vol. 184 t/m 187., 07-04-1948 t/m 12-04-1948; 1433
    - Records of Proceedings (afschriften van bandopnamen) vol. 188 t/m 191., 13-04-1948 t/m 16-04-1948; 1434
    - Records of Proceedings (afschriften van bandopnamen) vol. 192 t/m 194., 04-11-1948 t/m 08-11-1948; 1435
    - Records of Proceedings (afschriften van bandopnamen) vol. 195 t/m 198., 09-11-1948 t/m 12-11-1948; 1436
    - Meerderheidsvonnis: Part A, chapter 1 t/m 3, 1 deel; part B, chapter 4 t/m 6, 4 delen; lijst van errata., nov./dec. 1948; 1437
    - Part B, chapter 7 t/m 8; part C chapter 9 en 10, 2 delen; van het Meerderheids vonnis. Judgment for the far east (IMT) Annex A en Annex B., nov. 1948; 1438
    - Lijst van errata; Afwijkend vonnis van rechter Pal (India), 1439
    - Afwijkend vonnis van Rechter Pal, India (vervolg). Afwijkend vonnis van Rechter Mr. Röling (Nederland)., 12 nov. 1948; 1440
  - GESCHIEDWERK EN DIVERSE BESCHRIJVINGEN VAN HET RIJKSINSTITUUT VOOR OORLOGSDOCUMENTATIE., 50.
    - Bijvoegsels uit aanwinstenlijsten van diverse afdelingen, 50.1.
      - Voorlopige overzichten., 50.1.1.
        - Lijst no. 1. Voorlopig overzicht van uit Duitsland ontvangen fotocopieën van het IMT-U.S. Military Tribunal., 17 febr. 1948; 1441